{
  "Flashcards": [
    {
      "Question": "Arizona",
      "Answer": "Diamondbacks"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Atlanta",
      "Answer": "Braves"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Baltimore",
      "Answer": "Orioles"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Boston",
      "Answer": "Red Sox"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Chicago",
      "Answer": "Cubs"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Chicago",
      "Answer": "White Sox"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Cincinnati",
      "Answer": "Reds"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Cleveland",
      "Answer": "Guardians"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Colorado",
      "Answer": "Rockies"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Detroit",
      "Answer": "Tigers"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Houston",
      "Answer": "Astros"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Kansas City",
      "Answer": "Royals"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Los Angeles",
      "Answer": "Angels"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Los Angeles",
      "Answer": "Dodgers"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Miami",
      "Answer": "Marlins"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Milwaukee",
      "Answer": "Brewers"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Minnesota",
      "Answer": "Twins"
    },
    {
      "Question": "New York",
      "Answer": "Mets"
    },
    {
      "Question": "New York",
      "Answer": "Yankees"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Oakland",
      "Answer": "Athletics"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Philadelphia",
      "Answer": "Phillies"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Pittsburgh",
      "Answer": "Pirates"
    },
    {
      "Question": "San Diego",
      "Answer": "Padres"
    },
    {
      "Question": "San Francisco",
      "Answer": "Giants"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Seattle",
      "Answer": "Mariners"
    },
    {
      "Question": "St. Louis",
      "Answer": "Cardinals"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Tampa Bay",
      "Answer": "Rays"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Texas",
      "Answer": "Rangers"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Toronto",
      "Answer": "Blue Jays"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Washington",
      "Answer": "Nationals"
    }
  ]
}